(Penny:)Sweetie, I'm so sorry.
(Penny:)I wish there was something I could do
to make you feel better.
(Leonard:)-I do, too, but there's not.
-Really? Are you sure about that?
(Leonard:)Of course, who am I to argue
with a check-plus student?
(Leonard:)Just warning you,
I'm gonna go right.
(Leonard:)Don't make a big deal out of it.
(Stuart:)Is make-up really necessary?
(Raj:)Well, when someone looks
at your dating profile,
(Raj:)the first thing they see is
your picture.
(Raj:)I just want to make sure
you look fun and full of life
(Raj:)and not like a body
they just pulled out of the river.
(Raj:)All right, here we go,
and... smile.
(CAMERA CLICKS)
Okay. That one's in the bank.
(Raj:)How about this? Turn away,
and then tum back into it.